So to summarize our discussion of Recursive Descent Parsing, it's a simple in general
因此，总结一下我们对递归下降解析的讨论，一般来说，这是一个简单的
parsing strategy. You can parse any Context-Free Grammar using Recursive Descent,
解析策略。您可以使用递归下降来解析任何上下文无关文法，
so it's very general in that respect. It cannot work with Left-Recursive
所以在这方面是非常普遍的。它不能与左递归一起使用
Grammar so you must eliminate The Left Recursion. Now in principle,
语法，所以你必须去掉左递归。现在原则上讲，
this can be automatically. You can have Algorithms that will eliminate the
这可以是自动的。您可以使用算法来消除
Left Recursion. In practice, people eliminate the Left Recursion by hand and the
左递归。在实践中，人们用手来消除左递归，
reason for that is that you need to know what the grammar is that you're using
原因是您需要知道您正在使用的语法是什么
so that you can write the semantic actions. And we haven't talked about semantic
这样您就可以编写语义动作。我们还没有谈到语义
actions yet but we will see them shortly. And because you wanted to know exactly
目前还没有行动，但我们很快就会看到。因为你想确切地知道
what grammar, form of grammar it has, people generally do the elimination of
它有什么语法，它的语法形式，人们一般都是做消除的
left-recursion on their own. But that's not difficult to do. And in fact, recursion
它们自己的左递归。但这并不难做到。事实上，递归
descent is a popular strategy in practice. There are a lot to be more complicated,
在实践中，下降是一种流行的策略。还有很多事情要更复杂，
but actually compilers in fact with complicated grammars use recursive
但实际上，具有复杂语法的编译器使用递归
descent because it is so general. So, for example GCC is front-end
下降是因为它太笼统了。那么比如说GCC就是前端，
is a handwritten Recursive Descent Parser.
是一个手写的递归下降解析器。